<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-05-29T23:38:20-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Arturo R. Cabrera</title><subtitle>Developer blog where I document learnings, configurations, and neat things I discover throughout my coding journey.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello GitHub Pages</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/github/2019/06/05/hello-github-pages.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello GitHub Pages" /><published>2019-06-05T19:02:01-04:00</published><updated>2019-06-05T19:02:01-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/github/2019/06/05/hello-github-pages</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/github/2019/06/05/hello-github-pages.html"><![CDATA[<p>I have decided to create a GitHub Page.  I intend to use this site to document all the amazing things that a developer encounters.  At the moment, I am very interested in learning about React Native and .NET Core Framework.  They are on completely different sides of the spectrum.  One is a skill I have to pick up for work.  The other one is something I have been very intersted in learning for a couple of years.</p>

<p>I work for <a href="https://mna.co">minds + assembly</a> as a lead developer in New York.  We work on a lot of different projects which allow me to touch many new technologies.  I also ensure to guide our teams in the best solutions and technologies we can provide to our clients.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="github" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have decided to create a GitHub Page. I intend to use this site to document all the amazing things that a developer encounters. At the moment, I am very interested in learning about React Native and .NET Core Framework. They are on completely different sides of the spectrum. One is a skill I have to pick up for work. The other one is something I have been very intersted in learning for a couple of years.]]></summary></entry></feed>